# **Justin Fevurly**

Digital Analyst Scottsdale, Arizona, 85251 (480) 888-5129

JGFevurly@email.arizona.edu

### **SELECT SKILLS**

Passionate, competitive, goal-oriented, and collaborative marketer who is always learning. Talented problem solver and creative thinker with experience devising innovative analytical solutions to unexpected challenges. Skilled multitasker with a superior work ethic, good teamwork, and organizational skills. Reliable and dedicated team player with a hardworking and resourceful approach.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Digital Marketing Intern** Keap (Infusionsoft) Software Company, Chandler, AZ 6/2022 - 11/2022

- Authored creative, unique, and appealing sales and marketing presentations and collateral
  materials to engage discerning B2B and SaaS business clients by optimizing KPIs (key
  performance indicators) for our Keap sales and marketing automation. Experience using and
  analyzing competing CRMs, email marketing, e-commerce, appointment scheduling, and lead
  analytics tools
- Worked collaboratively in cross-functional teams with marketing, sales, vendors, and agency partners
- Demonstrated superior project management skills by coordinating meetings between project members and clients to develop ideas, discuss progress, and set goals
- Analytically astute digital and tech-savvy marketer effectively using data-driven approaches and a full suite of automation tools
- Excellent technical abilities and experience in Drupal, Airtable, InDesign, Marketo, Canva,
   Google Analytics and Microsoft programs
- Created workflow process for requesting, creating, editing, publishing and retiring sales and marketing content

Retirement Investment Service Intern Nationwide Insurance, Scottsdale, AZ 11/2021 - 1/2022

- Evaluated business or individual customer needs and financial situations to propose individualized policy recommendations
- Planned, developed, and implemented strategies to educate and support government employees with their retirement plans
- Anticipated questions and predictable pain points, prepared and delivered clear and articulate answers to inform the participants

Customer Experience Manager/Server Zipps Sports Bar, Scottsdale, AZ 4/2021 - 9/2021

- Created a positive, fun, and collaborative working environment by volunteering to help other servers in a team approach; established and demonstrated teamwork standards for service crew
- Communicated effectively with customers to plan large, specialized orders and events, provided recommendations, encouraged trial of new or featured items, and ensured food preparation was to customers' requested standards through strong attention to detail

• Meticulously organized and ensured clean workspaces to maximize productivity and safety

**Sales Leader** Puppies N' Love, Scottsdale, AZ 9/2018 - 1/2020

- Negotiated high-value investment in purebred and designer puppies
- Demonstrated ability to rapidly develop a relationship with potential customers and quickly access desires, and needs to propose the ideal fit
- Resolved customer concerns and turned the potential negative issues into positive experiences and long-term loyalty
- Increased customer engagement through personal connections with repeat customers that increased sales and customer satisfaction
- Happily and successfully homed over 100 dogs to loving and fitting families

#### **EDUCATION**

**Master of Science: Digital Audience Strategy** Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ 1/2022 - 12/2022

Cum Laude; GPA: 3.6; Completed professional development in Digital Audience Strategy

Bachelor of Arts: English: Creative Writing University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ

8/2019 - 5/2021

Magna Cum Laude, GPA: 3.7; Dean's List all Semesters

#### AWARDS/LEADERSHIP

Senior Patrol Leader 1/2019-7/2019

Awarded Eagle Scout 6/18

• Led troop of 63 scouts including 5 Patrol Leaders to all meetings, 9 campouts, and planned and executed skill development activities

Youth Counsellor Camp Civitan, Phoenix, Arizona 4/2018-6/2018

- Oversaw day-to-day activities of differently abled children participating in summer camp
- Collaborated with team members to promote safe activities and personal growth projects
- Developed team communications and information for meetings

Captain, Club Volleyball Team and Brophy JV, Brophy College Prep, Phoenix, AZ 2018, 2017, 2016